officialemailmarketing.com 2016-11-23

# Bulk Email Marketing Support

**Privacy Policy**  
www.officialemailmarketing.com is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. Should you choose to provide your Email address or any other personal information on any of the forms found on our site; you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with www.officialemailmarketing.com (owned by Official Internet Marketing). This privacy policy is intended for all users of www. officialemailmarketing.com. While at the moment we may or may not be collecting your personal information, we still want to inform you of what we will do with this information in the future. Therefore, some of these terms won't currently be applicable, but we will abide by these terms when a particular term does become valid.   
By visiting this web site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services. 

**In this privacy policy, you will find information on these areas:**   
What personally identifiable information www. officialemailmarketing.com collects.   
What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Website. What organization collects the information.  
How www.officialemailmarketing.com uses the information.   
With whom www.officialemailmarketing.com may share user information.   
What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.   
What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under www.officialemailmarketing.com control.   
How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.   
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact www.officialemailmarketing.com.   
Any violation of this privacy policy will lead to suspension of use privileges and permanent removal from this web site. 

**Information Collection and Use**

**Information Collection**  
www.officialemailmarketing.com is the sole owner of the information collected on our site. www.officialemailmarketing.com collects and monitors information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

**Registration**   
In order to get some information from this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user may be required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. You may also be asked to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as, username and password), so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. Please safeguard your password and other personal information. You may be liable for unauthorized use of our web site, as well as have your private information used by others.   
Unless you opt-out, you give www.officialemailmarketing.com permission to use your information as per this privacy policy.   
While www.officialemailmarketing.com will make every effort possible to protect your privacy, we do not promise, nor should you expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. This will include parties who attempt to illegally enter our web site and intercept or access transmissions or private communications.   
There will be instances when your information will be sold/given to third parties, AND THIS MAY BE IMMEDIATELY AFTER YOU REGISTER/PROVIDE YOUR E-MAIL ADDRESS AT THIS WEB SITE. However, unless described otherwise in this privacy policy, we will not sell any information. All information collected will be used solely by www.officialemailmarketing.com, unless mentioned otherwise in this privacy statement. 

**Information Use**

**Profile**   
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user’s personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Website, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties, unless specifically mentioned in this agreement. 

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.   
Cookies, if used, will be used on our site to remember and recall login names, login information, previous purchases, potential purchases, as well as other items to help us better understand user's needs. By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the "Profile" section.   
Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers or software providers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. These parties use of cookies are subject to their own set of privacy policies. 

**Log Files**   
Like most standard Web site servers we may use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Third Party Advertising**   
There is some information that is given to third party advertisers. Information about users' visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an Ad. This may include the data collected, such as your name, addresses and demographics, and is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about third party advertisers, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please contact us at the comments section on the web site.   
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.officialemailmarketing.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Communications from the Site**

**Special Offers and Updates**  
We may send all new members a welcoming email to your information, and if applicable, verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections. 

**Service Announcements**   
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Customer Service**   
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services. In regards to issues relating to their account we will reply via email. 

**Other uses**   
We can use your information to help facilitate requested information, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, enforce user agreements, analyze site usage, as well as site content customization, layout and services. Your information, such as your user ID and e-mail address, can be used with message boards and instant messaging. No personal information will be used here though. 

**Sharing**

**Legal Disclaimer**   
Other than when we provide your personal information to third parties, we make every effort to preserve user privacy. However, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. This includes, but is not limited to, any defense to any claim in which www.officialemailmarketing.com in a defendant, to assist in any investigations by law enforcement agencies, or violations of any www.officialemailmarketing.com policy. 

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**   
If you opt out, www.officialemailmarketing.com will not rent, sell or share your information in general, but there are certain instances that your information may be used. We may share aggregated demographic information and in some cases your e-mail address with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any other personally identifiable information. This is how your information will be shared: 

**To partners  
**Information relating to minors will only be used with prior parental or guardianship approval.   
If www.officialemailmarketing.com merges or sells part of its assets with another company, then this information will be shared with the merging company. 

**Third Party Advertisers:**   
We may share, sell or lease your information and your e-mail address with third party advertisers, and this will be used to gather information about users for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site and other sites. The information they collect and share through this technology may or may not be personally identifiable, other than your e-mail address. For more information or for choices about not having this information used please email us to opt out support@officialemailmarketing.com. 

**These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information:**   
www.officialemailmarketing.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you may have  requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances (if and when they should become applicable):   
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with www.officialemailmarketing.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help www.officialemailmarketing.com communicate with you about offers from www.officialemailmarketing.com and our marketing partners.  
We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing www.officialemailmarketing.com to collect and use their child's information without consenting to www.officialemailmarketing.com sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes. We will not ask for more information from children than is necessary to participate in this web site, when eligible to participate;   
We may sell your personal information to third party advertisers whom www.officialemailmarketing.com feels you, the user would have an interest in. While we believe in the integrity of the advertisers, www.officialemailmarketing.com has no control over the content of these ads and will not be liable for its content.   
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;   
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of www.officialemailmarketing.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law;   
We transfer or lease information about you if www.officialemailmarketing.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, www.officialemailmarketing.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy;   
www.officialemailmarketing.com may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, age, gender and geographical areas;   
www.officialemailmarketing.com does not necessarily provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted Ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad;   
We do not support any illegal use of your private information and will make every effort to stop such practices in order to protect your privacy. 

**Third Party Intermediaries**   
If ever applicable, we may use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Service Providers**   
We may partner with other third parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, or other contact information. This information will include e-mail address' and other information (which will be described at a later date when we use a particular service provider. which will be necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Business Transitions**   
In the event www.officialemailmarketing.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via e-mail, as well as with a prominent notice on our Web site for at least 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. 

**Children's privacy.**   
www.officialemailmarketing.com is designed for those who can legally create binding contracts. Therefore, www.officialemailmarketing.com wants to protect children's privacy. We comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and its accompanying FTC regulations. 

**Choice/Opt-out**   
Users who no longer wish to receive our communications may opt-out of receiving these communications contacting us via our web site.   
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties (that is not already mentioned here). We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. 

**Links**   
This Web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, www.officialemailmarketing.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. www.officialemailmarketing.com may have co-branding and/or framing relations with other companies. In this case, you should be familiar with the privacy policies of both companies, since you may be subject to each of them. www.officialemailmarketing.com WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY ACTIONS OF THIRD PARTIES WHOM YOU HAVE INTERACTED WITH FROM OUR SITE. 

**Surveys & Contests **   
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary but the information collected may be disclosed as per this privacy agreement. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used/shared with the contest/survey sponsors (if any) to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Unless mentioned in this privacy policy, users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.   
www.officialemailmarketing.com can not be liable for the actions of any "friend" who may give out your personal information, other than what is permitted in this privacy policy. Any abuse of this service will lead to suspension or termination of use of this website. 

**Security**   
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.   
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information, if ever applicable, (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'.   
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment.   
www.officialemailmarketing.com will make every effort to protect your information. However, www.officialemailmarketing.com can't be liable (for any damages whatsoever) for security breaches that occur outside of www.officialemailmarketing.com.   
If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can contact us on our web site. 

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**   
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done on line with www.officialemailmarketing.com. 

**Notification of Changes**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.   
If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
